<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide App</string>
    <string name="kampala_description">
        Kampala is Uganda\'s national and commercial capital bordering
        Lake Victoria, Africa\'s largest lake. Hills covered with
        red-tile villas and trees surround an urban centre of contemporary
        skyscrapers. In this downtown area, the Uganda Museum explores
        the country\'s tribal heritage through an extensive
        collection of artefacts. On nearby Mengo Hill is Lubiri
        Palace, the former seat of the Buganda Kingdom

    </string>

    <string name="kampala_moreInfo">

        Elevation: 1,190 m\nArea: 189 km²\nWeather:
        19°C, Wind W at 6 km/h, 94%
        Humidity\nLocal time: Tuesday
        03:15\nPopulation: 1.507 million (2014) United Nations

    </string>

    <string name="detail1">
    Details\n\n
    A premier restaurant offering the finest
    dining experience, and bar offering one of Kampala\'s most celebrated night experiences.Cayenne.
    it rocks!!!\n\nCUISINES\n
    Italian, Indian, Bar, Pizza, International, Pub\n\nMEALS\nBreakfast, Lunch, Dinner, Late
    Night\n\n

    FEATURES\nDelivery, Takeout, Highchairs Available,Outdoor Seating, Buffet, Seating, Street
    Parking,Accepts American Express, Accepts Mastercard,Accepts Visa, Free Wifi,
    Reservations,Parking Available, Television, Serves Alcohol,Full Bar, Table Service, Live Music
    </string>
    <string name="detail2">

    Details\n\nCUISINES\nAfrican\n\nSPECIAL DIETS\nVegetarian Friendly, Vegan Options
    \n\nMEALS\nLunch, Dinner\nFEATURES\nTakeout, Seating, Wheelchair Accessible, Delivery,
    Reservations, Table Service
    </string>

    <string name="detail3">

    Details\n\nPRICE RANGE\nUGX 18,450 - UGX 92,251\n\nCUISINES\nChinese\n\nMEALS\nLunch, Dinner,
    Late Night\n\nFEATURES\nReservations, Seating, Takeout,Outdoor Seating, Private Dining, Serves
    Alcohol, Full Bar, Table Service

    </string>
    <string name="detail4">

    SPECIAL DIETS\n\nVegetarian Friendly, Vegan Options\n\nMEALS\nLunch, Dinner, Late
    Night\n\nCUISINES\nItalian, Mediterranean, European, Pizza\n\nFEATURES\nReservations, Seating,
    Parking Available, Wheelchair Accessible,\nServes Alcohol, Full Bar, Table Service, Outdoor
    Seating, Highchairs Available
    </string>

    <string name="detail5">

    Details\n\nCUISINES\nBar, International, European\n\nSPECIAL DIETS\nVegetarian Friendly, Vegan
    Options\n\nMEALS\nBreakfast, Lunch, Dinner, Brunch\n\nFEATURES\nHighchairs Available,
    Reservations, Outdoor Seating,Seating, Parking Available, Street Parking, Free Off-Street
    Parking, Serves Alcohol, Full Bar, Wine and Beer, Accepts Mastercard, Accepts Visa, Digital
    Payments, Free Wifi, Table Service, Takeout, Wheelchair Accessible
    </string>

    <string name="detail6">

    Details\n\nABOUT\nCafejavas is a full-service, quick-casual,
    coffee-themed restaurant chain in Kampala Uganda.
    It provides the perfect refuge from a busy days
    shopping or a quick break from the office.
    It is where Kampala goes for breakfast, lunch,
    dinner, coffee and pastries. Menu items are specifically
    designed to meet the needs of just about everyone looking
    for a friendly informal dining experience. Great emphasis
    is put on customer service. The staff are highly skilled,
    trained and experienced in the hospitality industry.
    We commit to great food, great coffee, great service,
    an experience that will make you long for more.\n\n
    PRICE RANGE\nUGX 18,450 - UGX 73,801\n\n
    SPECIAL DIETS\nVegetarian Friendly, Vegan Options, Halal, Gluten Free Options\n\n
    MEALS\nBreakfast, Lunch, Dinner, Brunch, Late Night\n\n
    CUISINES\nCafe, European, Contemporary\n\n
    FEATURES\nTakeout, Outdoor Seating, Seating, Parking Available,
    Street Parking, Validated Parking, Free Off-Street
    Parking, Highchairs Available, Wheelchair Accessible
    , Accepts Visa, Free Wifi, Reservations, Accepts
    Credit Cards, Table Service

    </string>
    <string name="detail7">

      Details\n\nPRICE RANGE\nUGX 18,450 - UGX 92,251\n\n

    CUISINES\nChinese\n\nMEALS\nLunch, Dinner, Late Night\n\nFEATURES\nReservations, Seating, Takeout,
        Outdoor Seating, Private Dining, Serves
        Alcohol, Full Bar, Table Service

    </string>

    <string name="detail8">

      Details\n\nPRICE RANGE\nUGX 18,450 - UGX 92,251\n\n

    CUISINES\nChinese\n\nMEALS\nLunch, Dinner, Late Night\n\nFEATURES\nReservations, Seating, Takeout,
        Outdoor Seating, Private Dining, Serves
        Alcohol, Full Bar, Table Service

    </string>

    <string name="detail9">

      Details\n\nPRICE RANGE\nUGX 18,450 - UGX 92,251\n\n

    CUISINES\nChinese\n\nMEALS\nLunch, Dinner, Late Night\n\nFEATURES\nReservations, Seating, Takeout,
        Outdoor Seating, Private Dining, Serves
        Alcohol, Full Bar, Table Service

    </string>

    <string name="detail10">

      Details\n\nPRICE RANGE\nUGX 18,450 - UGX 92,251\n\n

    CUISINES\nChinese\n\nMEALS\nLunch, Dinner, Late Night\n\nFEATURES\nReservations, Seating, Takeout,
        Outdoor Seating, Private Dining, Serves
        Alcohol, Full Bar, Table Service

    </string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="gadaffi_Mosque_Old_Kampala">Gadaffi_Mosque_Old_Kampala</string>
    <string name="Gadaffi_Mosque_Old_Kampala">
    I put this at numero uno mainly because it boasts the best view of all of Kampala from the top
    of its minaret. The mosque itself is also an impressive building and tourists are allowed to
    walk around it at will (even taking photos). \nBuilt by…yes you guessed it…former Libyan
    leader/dictator Colonel Gadaffi it is Kampala’s largest mosque. \nEntrance is 10,000 UGX and women
    are given a headscarf and sarong to cover up and then taken around by a guide. (pay in the
    office around the side of the building).

</string>
    <string name="kabakas_Palace_and_Idi_Amins_Torture_chambers">Kabakas_Palace_and_Idi_Amins_Torture_Chambers</string>
    <string name="Kabakas_Palace_and_Idi_Amins_Torture_Chambers">
    This is the historic seat of the Bugandan king, located on Mengo hill exactly one mile up from
    the Buganda parliament. It is largely unoccupied these days due to the horrific functions in
    took under the rules of Idi Amin and president Obote. \nAmin built his torture chamber here, which
    saw the murder of an estimated 300 people, basically anyone stronger or smarter than Amin or
    anyone he thought ugly… While you cant go in the palace itself you can get a guided tour around
    the torture chambers (10,000 UGX) which offers a harrowing, but important, insight into Uganda
    under Amin.\n Authentic messages of desperation written on the walls in human excrement and blood
    remain to tell the tale.
</string>

    <string name="ba_hai_Temple">Ba_hai_Temple</string>
    <string name="Ba_hai_Temple">
    Found on Kikaya Hill off the Gayaza rd this is the only one of its kind on the African continent
    and definitely worth a visit. Located quite far out of town (the other side of the northern
    bypass) it also boasts the best green space in the whole of Kampala, with extensive grounds,
    that if you’re not of a spiritual persuasion are a perfect picnic spot and place to spend a
    chilled out Sunday. \nIf you are of a spiritual nature or just curious about the Bah’ai faith then
    I recommend the Sunday service (starts at 10.30 am).
    </string>

    <string name="namirembe_Catherdral">Namirembe_Catherdral</string>
    <string name="Namirembe_Catherdral">
    Again, one of the main draws of this cathedral is the great view it has across Kampala. It is,
    however, in my opinion, also the most beautiful of Kampala’s Christian cathedrals.\n Word of
    warning though – ever since they started renovating it they try and charge any muzungu wandering
    around with a camera or looking vaguely touristy a 10,000 UGX donation towards the renovation
    (even if you don’t go in).\n My advice? Tell them you’re a) worshipping b) got to rush and meet
    some friends but will be back after and will pay then. For those of you interested in theology
    or looking to worship – this one’s a protestant church. After you’ve checked out the cathedral
    you can always also pop to Namirembe guest house for a spot of lunch or down to nearby Java’s
    for a coffee.
    </string>

    <string name="owino_Market">Owino_Market</string>
    <string name="Owino_Market">
    Part of the old taxi park in central Kampala. A ‘dirty mental chaos’ is probably the best words
    to describe Owino and the taxi park! It’s the kind of place you might go in to with 5 friends
    and come out alone and inexplicably missing your left shoe…Nevertheless it is definitely an
    experience worth having just to appreciate the hecticness of everyday life and get a contrast to
    Kololo’s manicured lawns. \nThe market sells nearly anything you can think of, but the best buys
    for foreigners are on the African print fabrics sold here by length, and the wide range of
    second-hand clothes and shoes, including many designer labels – I’ve got a great Ralph Lauren
    jumper from there…! \nThere is also quite an interesting Voodoo market, selling all sorts of wierd
    and wonderful things if you can manage to negotiate the maze and find it! As always make sure to
    haggle and keep your personal belongings close and don’t wear any obvious jewelry or big
    handbags.
    </string>

    <string name="lake_Victoria">Lake_Victoria</string>
    <string name="Lake_Victoria">
    Obviously you couldn’t come to Uganda and NOT check out the second largest freshwater lake in
    the world! A good way to see the lake is by taking a short boat tour on it. \nYou can get a half
    day boat cruise for around US $80 from Kampala, or even out to Ngamba Chimp Island to see some
    wildlife (about a 45 minute trip depending on the weather). \nYou can also get a sunset cruise for
    25,000 UGX leaving from the Beach House (next to Kampala University), Ggaba at 5.30pm and
    arriving in Mukono at 11pm with Beach House cruises (tel: 0772435667 / 0752 280100 / 0782
    282028) and I’ve heard of people asking fishermen down at the lakeside by Port Bell informally
    to take them out on the lake and doing a 45-minute trip to Ggaba road fish market for lunch and
    then back for around 40,000 UGX. \nTop your trip off with some fresh tilapia on the lakeside at
    Sssese Islands gateway beach (about 30-40mins outside Kampala off the Entebbe road) or the other
    numerous lakeside joints and then head up to Cassia lodge hotel (on Buziga Hill just off the
    Gabba road) for a cocktail to watch the sun set over the lake. Aaah peeerfect.
    </string>

    <string name="craft_Markets">Craft_Markets</string>
    <string name="Craft_Markets">
    While Uganda may not be know within Africa for its crafts – and lets be honest a lot of them are
    imported from nearby Kenya and DRC – there is still, however, some good local stuff being made,
    and whether you’re decorating your house, buying your family 20 identical but ‘authentic’
    Christmas presents or just looking for some souvenirs of your time here, the Kampala craft
    markets offer some good options. \nThe largest craft market is on Buganda rd, central Kampala and
    is open 7 days a week. Be careful to shop around and haggle before buying anything. \nCheaper and
    often better, however, is the Jukali handicraft village – better known as the ‘Friday craft
    market’ up in Nsambya, off Gabba rd. It operates to some extent every day but as you can guess
    from the name only really comes into full force on Fridays. It has a good selection of artwork,
    jewelry, wooden and stone sculptures as well as a small amount of fabrics.
    </string>

    <string name="entebbe_Botanical_Gardens">Entebbe_Botanical_Gardens</string>
    <string name="Entebbe_Botanical_Gardens">
    Ok, so not technically speaking in Kampala, but if they can make Kampala’s international airport
    in Entebbe then I think I can include it in this list. \nEntrance to the gardens is 3,000 UGX for
    locals and 10,000 UGX for foreigners. It is definitely worth picking up a guide at the entrance
    as well, for a bit of background and explanations – including a demo of Tarzan’s vine
    rope-swinging. Payment of the guide is whatever you want to give them (more or less) but we were
    so impressed with ours when we went we were happy to pay a lot for his time. \nFor those plant and
    bird lovers out there there are over 300 different species of plant and countless birds
    including sunbirds, weavers and eagles. \nThe gardens are open 7 days a week from 9am- 7pm.
    Located just off the Entebbe road before Entebbe town on Berkeley road.
    </string>

    <string name="the_Uganda_National_Museum">The_Uganda_National_Museum</string>
    <string name="The_Uganda_National_Museum">
    Found on Kira rd it is the biggest and oldest museum in Kampala. Purporting to showcase Uganda’s
    cultural heritage with displays of ethnological and natural-historical exhibits. It could
    definitely do with a bit of a spruce up, creative revamp and a dusting. \nIt is in fact a bit like
    being stuck in a fantasy movie where the long forgotten exhibits come to life at night or
    transport you to an alternative universe…still it is the main museum in Kampala and for those
    with a passion for knowledge and artefacts (or a sense of humour) it may still be worth a visit.
    \nOpening hours are Monday to Saturday (10.00am to 6.00pm), Sunday and Public Holidays (12 Noon to
    6.00pm) and entrance is 1,000 UGX (500 shillings for children) for Ugandans and 3,000 UGX (1,500
    UGX for children) for foreigners. If you want to take photos it will cost an extra 5,000 UGX and
    20,000 UGX to take a video.
    </string>

    <string name="rubaga">Rubaga Cathdral</string>
    <string name="Rubaga_Cathdral">
    Another Cathedral but this one is of the Catholic persuasion. Again this cathedral is located on
    one of Kampala’s many hills so views are great. Kampala is fabled to have 7 hills. It in fact
    has 22 but Rubaga is one of the original ones and, therefore, worth a visit for historical
    reasons. The cathedral also boasts a memorial to the first African Catholic bishop in Uganda
    martyred for the cause of bringing Catholicism to Uganda and is the current headquarters of the
    Catholic Church in Uganda. Entrance is free although voluntary contributions are welcome.
    </string>
    <string name="location">location</string>
    <string name="_213">213</string>
    <string name="_4_2_rating">4.2</string>
    <string name="name_of_restuarant">Name of restuarant</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="kampala">Kampala</string>
    <string name="capital_of_uganda">Capital of Uganda</string>
    <string name="lets_tour_kampala">Lets Tour Kampala</string>
    <string name="restuarant_name">Restaurants Name</string>

    <string name="Independence">Independence</string>
    <string name="independence">
    Description\n\n
    The Independence Monument, standing majestically at a height of 6 metres, is a must see if you
    are travelling to Kampala. The monument situated in the heart of the capital between the
    Sheraton Kampala Hotel, Grand Imperial Hotel and StanChart bank, is one of the most distinctive
    landmark of Uganda. Ugandas Independence Monument was constructed by former British Colonial
    Government just before Uganda celebrated its first independence on Tuesday 9th October 1962.The
    monument depicts a man unwrapping a child and raising the child to touch the sky. The sculpture
    signifies a new born country let free from colonialism and bondages. Today with the
    beautification around the monument, you need to carry your camera for the memorable capture of
    the sight.This is among kampala\'s top Attractions and best sight when doing city walks


    </string>

    <string name="Nantawetwa">Nantawetwa</string>
    <string name="nantawetwa">
    Description:\n\n
    Nantawetwa Junction honors His Majesty the King as He travels from His palace (Lubiri) to His
    office Bulange/ Parliament, He must pass through this roundabout with subjects on the sides.\n\n
    Consequently, no one else beside the king is allowed to pass through the Nantawetwa. The
    roundabout had seen many structural adjustments till the recent long drum monument. Its located in the middle of the Royal Mile road.


    </string>
    <string name="Leadership">Leadership</string>
    <string name="leadership">
        Description:\n\n
    The Statue of Leadership situated outside Amber House (Kampala road) may be considered as a
    cerebration of one of Uganda\'s major milestones - the introduction of electricity. Situated
    overlooking the Kampala road, the Statue of Leadership sculpture depicts Sir Apollo Michael
    Kawalya Kaggwa, who is perhaps best known for his vision and foresight in accelerating the
        kingdom’s development.


    </string>
    <string name="Centenery">Centenery</string>
    <string name="centenery">
        Description:
    The Centenary monument located at the popular Centenary Park in Kampala, along Jinja road and
    neighbouring Hotel Africana, was erected to commemorate a centenary of Kampala City Council\'s
    (the city planning and administrating body) existence and its contribution to social economic
    development of the city. The 6ft Centenary Monument of a treadmill protected by shields
    signifies progress. This memorial is also depicted on Twenty Thousand Uganda Shillings note
    (2010)


    </string>
    <string name="Wold_war">World War</string>
    <string name="wold_war">
    Description\n\n
    The World War Monument is reputed to be the oldest monument in Kampala. It was built in 1945 by
    the British colonial government.The monument standing at the Constitutional Square in Kampala
    near the fence of the Uganda High Court was built during the British era in memory of Uganda
    soldiers who died during the 1st and 2nd world wars. The 5ft monument is also depicted on the
    front side of the Uganda Shilling Five Thousand note (2010).


    </string>
    <string name="Stride">Stride</string>
    <string name="stride">
    Description\n\n
    Situated between the Uganda Parliament Gardens and Kampala Serena Hotel, the Stride Monument,
    was built in commemoration of Uganda hosting the Commonwealth Heads of Government Meeting
    (CHOGM) in 2007 and was unveiled by the Queen of England during the CHOGM summit. The Stride
    Monument is estimated to be the most expensive monument in Uganda with the work of its
    construction costing the country over Ush150 million. This a good sight to visit during your
    city walks

        Located between the Uganda Parliament Gardens and Kampala Serena Hotel, Kampala central, UGANDA
    </string>
    <string name="independence_monumnet">Speke Road, Kampala, Uganda</string>
    <string name="nantaweta_monumnet_Location">Kabaka Anjagala Road, Kampala, Uganda</string>
    <string name="cantenery_monumnet_location">Centenary Park, Kampala</string>
    <string name="leadership_monument_location">Amber House Ltd, Speke Road, Kampala</string>
    <string name="world_war_monument_location">Kampala-jinja road, Kampala</string>
    <string name="stride_monument_location">City Square, Martyrs\\\' Road</string>
    <string name="kabaka_palce_location">Mengo close</string>
    <string name="bahai_location">Bahai Kampala</string>
    <string name="namirembe_location">Namirembe Road Kampala</string>
    <string name="owino_location">Kampala-jinja road, Kampala</string>
    <string name="lakevictoria_location">south East Uganda</string>
    <string name="entebbe_botanical_location">Lumumba Avenu Uganda</string>
    <string name="craftsmarket_location">Ternan Ave, Kampala</string>
    <string name="meuseum_location">Haandi kampala restaurant ltd</string>
    <string name="rubaga_location">Colville St, Kampala</string>
    <string name="details_putintent">details</string>
    <string name="name_intent">name</string>
    <string name="position_intent">position</string>
    <string name="bitmap_intent">byteArray</string>
    <string name="elevation_name">Elevation:</string>
    <string name="elevation_value">1,190 m</string>
    <string name="area_word">Area:</string>
    <string name="area_value">189` km²</string>
    <string name="weather_word">Weather:</string>
    <string name="weather_values">22°C, Wind NW at 10 km/h, 85% Humidity</string>
    <string name="population_word">Population:</string>
    <string name="population_values">1.507 million (2014) United Nations</string>
    <string name="ambiance_name">Ambiance Kampala</string>
    <string name="ambiance_locaton">Street 1 Kampala road</string>
    <string name="guvnor">Guvnor</string>
    <string name="guvnor_location">Kambago close</string>
    <string name="hive">Hive Mukono</string>
    <string name="hibe_location">Mufumbira Kampala</string>
    <string name="sky_lounge">sky Louge</string>
    <string name="sky_location">Indonesia street Kampala</string>
    <string name="panemera">Panamera</string>
    <string name="panamera_location">Wankulukuku road, Kampala</string>
    <string name="legends">Legends</string>
    <string name="legends_location">Lugogo close Uganda</string>
    <string name="amnesia">Amnesia</string>
    <string name="amnesia_location">Paliament avenu Uganda</string>
    <string name="nyondo">Nyondo Club</string>
    <string name="nyondo_location">Tennis Ave, Kampala</string>
    <string name="wave">Wave Logue</string>
    <string name="wave_location">Rugby Club</string>
    <string name="obligatto">Obligato</string>
    <string name="obligato_location">Obligato close, Kampala</string>
    <string name="cayen">Cayenne Restaurant and Lounge</string>
    <string name="cayen_location">Kira Rd, Kampala</string>
    <string name="two_K_restuarant">2K Restaurant</string>
    <string name="two_k_location">Hoima Rd, Kampala</string>
    <string name="cayen_rates">4.1</string>
    <string name="cayen_raters">1,447 Google reviews</string>
    <string name="two_k_rates">4.2</string>
    <string name="two_k_raters">731 Google reviews</string>
    <string name="patio_restuarant">Il Patio Italian Restaurant</string>
    <string name="patio_location">Kisozi Close, Kyagwe Rd, Kampala</string>
    <string name="patio_raters">394 Google reviews</string>
    <string name="patio_rates">4.3</string>
    <string name="piato_restuarant">Piato</string>
    <string name="piato_location">Lumumba Ave, Kampala</string>
    <string name="piato_rates">4.3</string>
    <string name="piato_raters">1,279 Google reviews</string>
    <string name="cafe_javas">Cafe Javas - Kampala Road</string>
    <string name="cafe_javas_location">Kampala Road, Opposite post office, Kampala</string>
    <string name="cafe_rates">4.5</string>
    <string name="cafe_raters">1,333 Google reviews</string>
    <string name="faze_two">Faze 2</string>
    <string name="faze_two_location">Plot 10 Nakasero Road</string>
    <string name="faze_two_rates">4.1</string>
    <string name="faze_two_raters">630 Google reviews</string>
    <string name="amagar_restuarant">Amagara Cafe Bistro</string>
    <string name="amagara_location">Colville St, Kampala</string>
    <string name="amagara_raters">313 Google reviews</string>
    <string name="amagara_rates">4.1</string>
    <string name="haudai_retsuarant">Haandi kampala restaurant ltd</string>
    <string name="haudai_location">Haandi kampala restaurant ltd</string>
    <string name="haudai_raters">618 Google reviews</string>
    <string name="haudai_rates">4.2</string>
    <string name="seven_seas_restuarant">Seven Seas</string>
    <string name="seven_seas_location">Ternan Ave, Kampala</string>
    <string name="seven_seas_raters">26 Google reviews</string>
    <string name="seven_seas_rates">4.2</string>
    <string name="fang_fang_restuarant">Fang Fang Chinese Restaurant</string>
    <string name="fang_fang_location">Plot 1, Conville Street</string>
    <string name="fang_fang_raters">284 Google reviews</string>
    <string name="fang_fang_rates">4.1</string>


</resources>
